sochnews.tv 2013-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Soch News |Live TV |Talk shows | Columns|Breaking News

**Privacy Policy for[www.sochnews.tv](http://www.sochnews.tv/)**

The videos (Offline or Live) are and posted by the users of this website which are mostly from YouTube, Justin.tv, dailymotion and Facebook. If you want to Remove some video content from this website then immediately send an email to [sochnews@gmail.com](mailto:sochnews@gmail.com), we can delete the post and respond immediately. (Within 20 minutes to 1 hour) You can also fill online form http://www.sochnews.tv/contact-us/If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [sochnews@gmail.com  ](mailto:sochnews@gmail.com)

At www.sochnews.tv the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected.

**_Advertisers:_**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Ad sense, extend media, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**_Log Files_**

Like many other Web sites [www.sochnews.tv](http://www.sochnews.tv/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**_Cookies and Web Beacons_**

[www.sochnews.tv](http://www.sochnews.tv/) does not use cookies.

**_Double-click DART Cookie_**

Google or any other third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on [www.sochnews.tv. ](http://www.sochnews.tv/)Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.sochnews.tv](http://www.sochnews.tv/)and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

**Google Ad sense**

Chitika

Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.sochnews.tv](http://www.sochnews.tv/)send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[www.sochnews.tv](http://www.sochnews.tv/)  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.sochnews.tv](http://www.sochnews.tv/)’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**_Terms of Service_**

 This page outlines the core principals which you must abide by when using this website. In the circumstances which this document uses the terms “We”, “SochNews.Tv”, “Us” or “SochNews.Tv” outlines the owners, moderators and administrators which have created, developed and moderated this website (www.sochnews.tv)

 In the Events that the terms “You” or “Users” arise in this document then you should clearly understand that this means the users browsing the website.

 The term “the website” clearly defines “www.sochnews.tv”.

 We DO NOT host any videos on this website. All videos found on our site are found freely available around the web on sites such as DailyMotion.com, Justin.tv, Ustream.tv, Self cast, Zshare.net, YouTube Etc. We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated nor claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of videos/streams played on our site. All content is copyright of their respective owners.

 We urge all copyright owners, to recognize that links contained within this site are located somewhere else on the web. The embedded link points to the location of the video on the web. Please direct all copyright infringement issues to the companies that host these files (Daily Motion, ZeemTv, Justin.tv, Ustream.tv, Freed cast, YouTube, Zshare, MegaVideo Etc) If you still want to contact us email us [sochnews@gmail.com](mailto:sochnews@gmail.com)

 Terms and Conditions of using this website.

Although every care is taken in the preparation of the Website, you acknowledge that it is not technically possible to run the Website free of all faults, and we give no warranties as to the continued operation of the Website and accept no liability for any time the Website is not operational due to faults or maintenance.

You understand that the information supplied to us is by a third party and as such, we cannot take responsibility for this information. We fully appreciate the work of our third parties and take no credit for their efforts.

The material on the Website is designed to comply with Pakistani law and we cannot be held responsible for any non-compliance with applicable local laws in any other jurisdiction.

 Links to and from this Website

The Website may contain hypertext links to websites operated by third parties. We do not have control of such websites and you therefore acknowledge that we have no responsibility or liability for their content.

 The information provided from this website is not owned by us. In this instance we cannot take responsibility for what you do with this information and may be re-distributed with consent of its original authors.
